Ah, E3
It's like Christmas for gamers
But without family.
And way more alcohol.
Today I'm going to announce the 2017 winner
But to be completely honest this thing is unwinable
Electronics Arts first out, and start talking about some sci-fi sport
Then the boss man comes out and says:
"stop talking shit about Battlefront you fucking cunts" (Australian accent)
Russia coming to Battlefield... guys...
This is your one chance to add World War One track suits
In FIFA the singleplayer continues from the last game
and...yeah. We get it EA, you have money.
Two years ago they released a Need for Speed reboot, and now a Need for Speed 2
This is way different than the original.
Terrible remake, cancel it.
Prison break game! Where you need a friend to be able to play it.
So...that's not gonna happen.
Anthem a new game from super hot developer...Bioware.
And finally, what people actually showed up for.
Battlefront II will have 3x more content than the first one.
4 maps times 3...
Hey! That's a normal game!
Then a bunch of Youtubers played Battlefront but not me so who gives a fuck.
Publishers, I just want to say that I am extremely for sale.
I'll promote anything. I'll even say this for free...
EA won E3.
Microsoft is an American tech company. Therefore they need a buzz word or it collapses.
Today's word is four-k
They started by revealing that Project Scorpio is called Xbox One Two X. And is the strongest console ever.
Six times stronger than any PC.
They reveal like 42 exclusives and out of those 42, 2 were exclusives.
Games like Metro...without the metro.
Assassin's Creed:
"Subtitle Cliche"
Set in Hellenistic Egypt. I hope they do like Unity and give them all British accents.
A zombie survival game? Finally!
I don't care for these Twitch PvP games and I didn't understand the Destiny 2 trailer.
But now that I see the gameplay I don't think it's actually gonna look like this.
It's gonna look better, because 4k.
But seriously stop with the fake banter.
You can tell it's fake because no one called someone else an autistic sperglord.
But they did announce original backwards compatibility.
Meaning they re-announced Halo 2 so Microsoft wins E3.
Bethesda *Spoiler Alert* did not announce anything you wanted.
But it's at 6am in the morning so let's hope they don't dissapoint.
They announced DLC, a sequel to an average game, and paid mods.
People got...mildly provoked.
Bethesda defended themselves by saying "It's not mods it's paid mini-DLC!"
And the internet agreed and let it go.
But there was one more game
It went to black...the music started and. Elder Scrolls VI...
Nazi America!
It looks awesome. Great place to take the Elder Scrolls saga. Bethesda wins E3.
The conference that I assumed would have the most hype was Devolver Digital.
But they didn't announce Genital Jousting 2.
Joust Hard!
It was a fun little conference making fun of E3 conferences
Stay out of my territory!
But I always cheer for an underdog
So Devolver wins E3
The PC conference powered by AMD had the most exclusives.
They better have, PS4 and Xbox can both do 4K now.
So a PC is officially pointless
Total War: Warhammer 2 received some flak for not being historical?
What?! Do you guys not know dinosaurs existed?
Waifu Hearthstone...
Then Nvidia came out and talked about some nerd shit.
I like football so I zoned out. No idea what happened for the rest of the conference.
But they did show 40 seconds of Bannerlords, so IBM wins E3.
Ubi opened with XCom-Mario with Rabbids...WHAT?!
Nintendo wants that minion money
...more Assassin's Creed RPG
The Crew 2 has many vehicles but it's gonna be garbage without competitive forklifting.
Dharma initiative!
Then I was like is Rogue 2 happening? Awesome!
No it's a pirate game...alright
No! IT'S ANOTHER FUCKING PvP TWITCH MULTIPLAYER...FUCK! GOD!
I can't believe my biggest E3 disappointment was a new game.
Then things got worse...
Two years ago I joked that they showed Beyond Good and Evil 2.
Then they actually did it. Ubisoft stole my joke.
We get it Sony, you have money.
It started with an Uncharted spinoff...
Called Uncharted: Audio Problems
The only game I'm interested in is The Last of Witcher 3.
But it has zombie bears. Wouldn't they and other predators kill all the zombie humans?
Unless they're allies...
Then I want to be on Team Zombie!
Monster Hunter Dinosaurs...this E3 was all about dinosaurs.
HD Shadow of the Colossus.
...again.
Robot Revolution, where you play as the fucking toasters.
The baddies.
Yet it's Quantic Dream so it might be fun to fail every prompt.
God of War 4 is in Scandinavia, but Kratos is from ancient Greece so he can only speak American.
This will lead to some crazy misunderstandings.
I'm sure it will make a great sitcom.
But Frosted can understand what everyone is saying it won't be fun.
And finally Insomniac is making a new Spider-man similar to the classics.
But they don't understand what made them so good.
Tobey Maguire
James Franco wins E3.
Nintendo has returned to making bank so their conference had special effects.
Showed a weeb game where the gameplay looks good but the cut scenes look bad.
How do you mix them up?
Then they announced a Pokemon RPG for consoles.
Been requested for 20 years
That's the weakest way to announce the biggest announcement of E3.
Not sure how you would do it.
Like that! That's how you do it!
Finally, Super Mario Oddessey
Looks nothing like the book.
Didn't have any dinosaurs, and very few mexicans.
So they betrayed the book-readers but announced more stuff in 20 minutes than all other guys.
So the winner of E3...
Is Blizzard!
They started their own con.
And you lazy fools should too.
One con per company. No more E3 disappointments.